[Music]
easily jump to a Master entity with a
keyboard shortcut when you work with
data in business Central like for
example when entering sales lines you
often want to check things on the master
entity like the product you're about to
sell you can jump directly to the item
from the sales lines or any other place
where the item is referenced let's go to
a sales order to learn
how I open the tell me search with alq I
search for sales orders
and select sales orders from the
list I choose a random sales order in
this
case I now go to the item number on a
sales
line now to go directly to the item I've
selected here I can hold down the key
control and ALT and then choose the down
arrow so Control Alt down to jump
directly to the item you'll see the item
card opening here for this specific
product that's a great way an easy way
to jump to master entity with a keyboard
shortcut Control Alt down and this works
for any referenced field you can jump to
a customer you can jump to items and so
on this works anywhere in business
central control alt down thank you for
[Music]
watching